<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Aitor Martinez</title>
    <link>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Aitor Martinez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 15:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Graphics Library for Rasterized Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/rtg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/rtg/</guid>
      <description>This final year project aims to create a command-based Graphics Library that lets the user implement any advanced rasterized graphics techniques as easily as possible.The dissertation reflects the understanding of low-level APIs as well as advanced graphics techniques such as PBR and IBL.
Features  DirectX 12 Physically Based Rendering Image Based Lighting Deferred Rendering Fully dynamic lights Shadow Mapping Normal Mapping Parallax Mapping  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Town Stories</title>
      <link>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/oldtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/oldtown/</guid>
      <description>Old Town Stories is a VR (Oculus Rift) shooter game made with Unreal Engine 4.
Contribution  &amp;ldquo;VR integration: The player&amp;rsquo;s Pawn VR related input and hand animations integration.&amp;rdquo; VR optimization : Making sure the project had a stable 90 fps was a challenge due to the realistic look of the game. Some of the optimizations were: making sure there were no transparencies, level-streaming, using as simple as posible materials, HLODs, static lights&amp;hellip;&amp;quot; Magnetic Shield (gameplay): Shield which stops, accumulates and returns enemy bullets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arena of Warfare</title>
      <link>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/aow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/aow/</guid>
      <description>Arena of Warfare is a tower defense mobile game for Android devices. The main goal is to defend your base against enemy soldiers, planes and tanks. Made with Unity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gravity Shifter</title>
      <link>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/gravity/</guid>
      <description>Gravity Shifter is a 2D platformer game based on gravity, movement fluidity and slow motion.
The Challenge Gravity Shifter is played by using just the two joysticks on the controller. UI included. It was a design request made by my professor @SuperLemonBits!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ray Castings Demo</title>
      <link>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/raycasting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aitor-m.github.io/projects/creations/raycasting/</guid>
      <description>This voxel terrain is a low-level (ARM assembly) implementation of height-map rendering used in old-school games.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
